Exercise 7-9. Supporting words. For this next part of the intonation of grammatical
elements, each sentence has a few extra words to help you get the meaning. Keep
the same strong intonation that you used before and add the new stress where you
see the bold face. Use your rubber band. 1. The dogs eat the bones every day. 2.
The dogs ate the bones last week. 3. The dogs are eating the bones right now. 4.
The dogs will eat the bones if they're here. 5. The dogs will eat the bones if
they were here. 6. The dogs would have eaten the bones if they'd been here. 7.
The dogs that have eaten the bones are sick. 8. The dogs have eaten the bones
every day. 9. The dogs had eaten the bones by the time we got there. 10. The dogs
will have eaten the bones by the time we get there.